by RentAnAdviser.com
Know I have done wrong‚
left your heart torn
Is that what devils do?
Took you so long‚ where
only fools gone
I shook the angel in you!
Now I am rising from the crowd
Rising up to you!
Feel with all the strength I found
There′s nothing I can′t do!
I need to know now‚ know now
Can you love me again?
It is unforgivable
I stole and burnt your soul
Is that what demons do?
They rule the worst in me
Destroy everything
They blame on angels like you
Now I am rising from the ground
Rising up to you!
Filled with all the strength I found
There′s nothing I can′t do!
I need to know now‚ know now
Can you love me again?
Told you once I can′t do this again
Do this again!
I told you once I can′t do this again
I need to know now‚ know now
Can you love me again?
www.RentAnAdviser.com