Welcome to the party
We on fire
Step up in the party‚ step
up in the party‚ ha
We on fire
Ride up to the party‚ ride
up to the party‚ ha
Ay‚ live it up
Welcome to the party‚ ay
Hit them up ‚ get them up
Put them up ‚ we wakin′ up
Fly with my dogs‚ ridin′
high when we pull up
When we ride‚ when we pull up
We be high when we pull up
Coupe with the top down‚ no ceilings
Rocks on the watch now‚ armageddon
Roof on fire‚ fire‚ we ride wild
Pull up in a tank‚ bow bow
Yeah‚ on Ciroc‚ in the
drop‚ full of beans
Yeah‚ we the squad‚ 100
cars full of tings
Yeah‚ I pull up with fire
boy‚ the chinchilla
Yeah‚ It is Frenchy Montana‚
quilla and vanilla
Roof on fire‚ we be higher
like a whelie
Shawty bad‚ talkin′ MJ Thriller
Welcome to the party‚
sippin′ on the Act
Pull up in a ′Rari‚ DJ bring it back
Fell in love with shawty‚
money like Shaq
Welcome to the party (live it up)
Welcome to the party‚ ay
Burn up‚ let it burn
Burn up‚ let it burn (Lil Pump‚ ouu)
I am let it burn
Burn up‚ let it burn
I can′t feel my body ′cause I
pop a lot of molly (molly)
Welcome to the party‚ bitch‚
I am ′bout to catch a body
Punch him in his shit‚ we don′t
give a fuck about it
Bitch‚ I start a riot‚ bitch‚
I am ′bout to start a riot
Welcome to the trap ‚ got my
grandma selling crack
I make what you make in one year sitting
down just movin′ packs (damn)
Make a bitch do jumpin′ jacks
‚ like she was a acrobat
Got these bitches lookin′ at me
crazy ′cause I got face tats
Ouu‚ drip‚ drip‚ drip‚ I cannot
go wife a bitch (no)
Drop 5 million on my crib‚ now Lil
Pump is rich as shit‚ ouu
And I am still on my probation‚
pop a pill‚ I feel amazing
You just broke and you just hatin′‚
all these diamonds on me skatin′
Man‚ I do this every day‚ spend
three thousand on some shades
I got bitches in L.A.‚ your boyfriend
broke‚ his diamonds fake
Welcome to the party‚ ay
We on fire
Step up in the party‚ step
up in the party‚ haan
by RentAnAdviser.com