Perfect
I might never be your knight
in shining armor
I might never be the one you
take home to mother
And I might never be the one
who brings you flowers
But I can be the one‚
be the one tonight
When I first saw you
From across the room
I could tell that you were curious
Girl‚ I hope You are sure
What You are looking for
′Cause I am not good
at making promises
But if you like causing trouble
up in hotel rooms
And if you like having
secret le rendezvous
If you like to do the things you
know that we shouldn′t do
Baby‚ I am perfect
Baby‚ I am perfect for you
And if you like midnight driving
with the windows down
And if you like going places
we can′t even pronounce
If you like to do whatever You
have been dreaming about
Baby‚ You are perfect
So let′s start right now
I might never be the hand
you put your heart in
Or the arms that hold you
any time you want them
But that don′t mean that we can′t
live here in the moment
′Cause I can be the one you
love from time to time
When I first saw you
From across the room
I could tell that you were curious
Girl‚ I hope You are sure
What You are looking for
Cause I am not good at making promises
But if you like causing trouble
up in hotel rooms
And if you like having
secret le rendezvous
If you like to do the things you
know that we shouldn′t do
Baby‚ I am perfect
Baby‚ I am perfect for you
And if you like midnight driving
with the windows down
And if you like going places
we can′t even pronounce
If you like to do whatever You
have been dreaming about
Baby‚ You are perfect
So let′s start right now
And if you like cameras flashing
every time we go out
And if You are looking for someone to
write your breakup songs about
Baby‚ I am perfect
Baby‚ We are perfect
But if you like causing trouble
up in hotel rooms
And if you like having
secret le rendezvous
If you like to do the things you
know that we shouldn′t do
Baby‚ I am perfect
Baby‚ I am perfect for you
And if you like midnight driving
with the windows down
And if you like going places
we can′t even pronounce
If you like to do whatever You
have been dreaming about
Baby‚ You are perfect
So let′s start right now
www.RentAnAdviser.com